<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Roy Chancellor</title>
    <link>https://roychancellor.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Roy Chancellor</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://roychancellor.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Engineering Projects</title>
      <link>https://roychancellor.me/engineering_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roychancellor.me/engineering_projects/</guid>
      <description>Projects on this page illustrate reactive and proactive problem solving projects I worked on either directly as a team leader or as an advisor to the primary project team. The projects show how Shainin Red X and Green Y methods can quickly converge on the root cause of a technical problem.
Reactive Problem Solving Reactive problem solving occurs when a problem already exists and needs attention, whether it be for a line-down situation or to eliminate chronic problems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Programming Projects</title>
      <link>https://roychancellor.me/programming_projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://roychancellor.me/programming_projects/</guid>
      <description>All of my personal projects can be found on GitHub. Below are some projects that I am particularly proud of:
ProjectEuler Project Euler is a collection of challenging math problems solved with programming. I have used these problems for intellectual stimulation and to practice coding in Java. Problem descriptions are here. My repository is here and below are a few I am proud of:
 Problem #12: Find the first triangular number that has at least 500 divisors (has some cool optimizations) Problem #13: Find the first 10 digits of the sum of 100 fifty-digit numbers Problem #15: Find the number of paths through a 20 x 20 grid (this one was HARD&amp;hellip;there&amp;rsquo;s probably an easier way) Problem #16: Find the sum of the digits in 2^1000 (Wish I knew about BigDecimal before this one!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>